Now, we'll do the same thing for topics and words.
现在对主题和单词进行相同的运算
Let's say for the sake of visualization that we only have four words: space,
为了方便可视化 假设只有四个单词
climate, vote, and rule.
space climate vote 和 rule
Now we have a different distribution, beta.
现在有一个不同的分布 β
This one is similar to the previous one but it is three-dimensional,
这个分布和之前的相似 但是三维分布
is not around a triangle but it's around a simplex.
不是三角形 而是单纯形
Again, the red parts are high probability and the blue parts are low probability.
同样 红色部分表示很高的概率 蓝色部分表示很低的概率
If we had more words,
如果有更多单词
we would still have a very clear distribution except it would
则依然是非常清晰的分布
be in a much higher dimensional simplex.
但是维度更高的单纯形
This is why we picked four words because we can visualize that simplex in 3D.
因此我们选择了 4 个单词 这样可以用三维图形来表示
So, in this distribution beta,
在这个分布 β 中
we pick a random point and it will very likely be
我们选择一个随机的点
close to a corner or an edge. Let's say it's here.
它很有可能接近角落或边缘 假设在这里
This point generates the following multinomial distribution,
这个点生成了以下多项分布
0.4 for space, 0.4 for climate,
space 为 0.4 climate 为 0.4
and 0.1 for vote and rule.
vote 和 rule 都为 0.1
This multinomial distribution we'll be called phi and it
我们将这个多项分布称为 Φ
represents the connections between the words and the topic.
它表示单词和主题之间的关系
Now from this distribution,
我们从这个分布中
we will sample random words which are 40 percent likely to be space,
抽取随机单词 单词是 space 的概率为 40%
40 for climate, 10 for vote and 10 for rule.
是 climate 的概率为 40% 是 vote 和 rule 的概率都为 10%
The words could look like this.
单词可能是这样的
Now we do this for every topic.
我们对每个主题执行这一运算
So, Topic 1 is say around here close to Space and Climate,
假设主题 1 位于此处 接近 Space 和 Climate
topic 2 is here close to vote,
主题 2 位于此处 接近 vote
and on topic 3 is here close to rule.
主题 3 位于此处 接近 rule
Notice that we don't know what topics they are,
注意 我们不知道它们是什么主题
we just know them as topic 1, 2, and 3.
只知道是主题 1 2 和 3
After some inspection, we can infer that topic
观察之后 可以推断
1 being close to Space and Climate must be science.
接近 Space 和 Climate 的主题 1 肯定是科学
Similarly, topic 2 being close to vote could be Politics,
同样 接近 vote 的主题 2 可能是政治
and topic 3 being close to rule could be sports.
接近 rule 的主题 3 可能是体育
But this is something that we'd be doing at the end of the model.
这是在模型最后执行的操作
And as a final step,
最后一步 我们将这三个主题合并起来
we join these three together to obtain our other matrix in the LDA model.
获得 LDA 模型中的其他矩阵